[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
(This drama is a work of fiction)
(Any similarity to real people,
organizations, or events is coincidental)
[birds singing]
(Dareum) Mr. Kang.
(Hagi) Yes?
(Dareum) What do you think...
about me applying
for the Paris assignment?
[calm music]
[Dareum grunts]
I was just curious.
I'm learning a lot here right now,
but I wonder what it'd be like
to work in a different environment.
[faint laugh]
That would be nice.
Really?
Of course.
(Hagi) You should gain experience
in a different environment too.
And an employee's growth
would help the company as well.
You should apply.
What about you?
Me?
Are you fine with it?
[faint laugh]
Of course.
(Hagi) Paris is just
a plane ride away, you know.
[rustles]
[sighs]
[music stops]
[laughs]
[Mimi gasps]
(Mimi) Are you kidding me?
You barely just started dating
your first boyfriend.
[rattles]
(Seula) So what did he say?
(Mimi) He would've been shocked,
obviously.
He said it's okay.
(Mimi) What?
[Seula gasps]
[intriguing music]
He told me to go to Paris.
(Seula) Maybe he didn't know how to react.
He seemed sincere, though.
[Mimi inhales]
(Mimi) Hey, I know this
because I've done it myself.
You'll break up for sure
if you start a long-distance relationship.
(Dareum) Why?
Even Han Jeongyeon
wanted to steal your boyfriend.
(Mimi) Do you really think
women would leave him alone?
They'll steal him away.
[comical sound]
- (Dareum) What?
- (Seula) She's right.
You said dozens of women
asked him out at work too.
[cat hissing sound]
[grunts]
(Let's steal Kang Hagi)
[inhales]
[comical sound]
(women) Kang Hagi!
[women cheer]
(Mimi) No way.
You really can't do this.
[deflated sound effect]
[music stops]
[sizzling]
[wooden bell sound]
[chanson music]
[ding sound]
[kissing sound]
[Dareum exclaims]
[taps]
[baby laughing sound]
[Dareum laughs]
[sparkling sound]
(man) [in French] I love you, Dareum.
[swish sound]
(Dareum) I love you too.
[laughs]
[cute sound effects]
[blinking sound]
[bubble popping sound]
[sizzling]
[melting sound effect]
- (Minwoo) [in Korean] Hey!
- (Hagi) Oh, my gosh!
[music stops]
What's taking so long?
(Minwoo) I'm starving!
You've been cooking those dumplings
for ages!
Jeez, you scare me...
[intriguing music]
[clatters]
[thuds]
[can opening]
(Minwoo) Yes!
Wow. You burned it all.
This is all because you told her to go
to Paris when you didn't even mean it.
Oh, that's hot...
[comical sound]
[Hagi grunts]
Listen.
Dating is like a dumpling.
[comical sound]
You have to flip it when it's hot,
[whoosh sound]
then put it down to let it cool.
[swish sound]
You need a bit of distance
[comical sound]
to make it last longer.
Take a step back
to take two steps forward.
That's what dating experts do.
[comical sound]
[bubble popping sound]
[baby crying sound]
[popping sound]
Why does it have to be France?
[music stops]
They'll kiss her on the cheeks
whenever they say hi.
I don't like it.
Are you worried already?
- No, I'm not.
- (Minwoo) You are!
Hey, just be chill and let her go.
Don't be such a loser.
[whoosh sound]
[playful music]
It'll be over if you go.
(Mimi) You'll break up for sure.
[whoosh sound]
You have to let her go
for your relationship to last!
(Minwoo) Just be cool and let her go!
[whoosh sound]
Never.
No!
[buzzer beeping sound]
[swish sounds]
(Minwoo) Go!
(Mimi) No!
[buzzer beeping sound]
(Minwoo) Go!
(Mimi) No!
[buzzer beeping sound]
[music stops]
[Dareum groans]
(Final Episode)
[birds singing]
[wind blowing]
[biting sound]
[intriguing music]
[knocking]
[clatters]
[music stops]
(Hagi) Yes?
[door opens]
(Miyeong) Mr. Kang.
[door closes]
Did you see the notice from HAN?
[mouse clicking]
Oh, not yet.
(Miyeong) It's a request
for a seconded employee.
"We strongly hope that Ms. Nam Dareum
[intriguing music]
will be seconded to us."
That's what it says.
[wooden bell sound]
[whoosh sound]
[sparkling sound]
We haven't confirmed
whether Ms. Nam is willing yet.
Then ask her.
(Miyeong) Pardon?
Let's reply that we'll give the request
favorable consideration
if Ms. Nam is willing.
"Favorable consideration"?
(Hagi) Yes. That would be nice.
The growth of an employee
[ding sound]
leads to the growth of our company.
[whoosh sound]
[claps]
[fanfare sound]
Growth for everyone.
[popping sound]
[cheering sound]
[laughs]
[laughs awkwardly]
[Hagi claps]
Mr. Kang...
Are you really okay with that?
Of course.
[baby crying sound]
[dripping sound]
[laughs awkwardly]
All right, then...
[music stops]
[laughs]
[Hagi grunts]
[Miyeong laughs awkwardly]
[intriguing music]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[phone vibrating]
[music stops]
[message notification sound]
(Minwoo) Hey. I just saw Choi Sungwook.
Here's the address.
[faint sigh]
(Car Wash)
[splashing]
(owner) You'll never finish at this rate.
Hurry up, everyone!
Did you wipe over here?
You didn't wipe the wheel here.
Get this part too.
- Mr. Choi. Don't just wipe there.
- (Sungwook) Yes?
(owner) Wipe the top too.
Yes, sir.
(owner) Don't be so gentle. Wipe harder.
(Sungwook) Yes, sir.
[calm music]
(owner) Jeez...
[birds singing]
[street sounds]
[music stops]
[wind blowing]
(Hagi) Did you quit just to do this?
Why did you do it
when you couldn't even make it big?
Well...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
(Hagi) Why didn't you send them
the final version?
[smacks lips]
Because I'm an idiot.
[scoffs]
I couldn't bear
to see you actually get screwed.
[calm music]
(Sungwook) Do you remember...
when we first got our office for APPELLO?
We moved boxes all night,
and when the servers crashed,
we'd practically live
at the office for days.
How could I...
forget about all that?
What I did gave me some breathing room...
but it only made me feel worse afterward.
I thought, "What am I even doing?"
But I guess this is for the best.
Do you think anyone
would admire you for that?
You should've just screwed me over
properly and made a killing!
(Hagi) I still...
hate you so much for it.
That's only right.
(Sungwook) Hagi.
It wasn't your fault...
that I ended up like this.
And it's not because you succeeded.
It's just...
[sighs]
I...
couldn't even cheer you on.
I hated myself for having
such petty feelings.
And I couldn't bear it.
I really am sorry.
And thank you...
for at least giving me
a chance to explain.
(owner) Mr. Choi!
Don't you see we're busy here?
(Sungwook) Coming, sir!
Hagi.
I still feel...
grateful to you.
Bye.
[footsteps fading]
[sniffles]
[music stops]
(Overseas Assignment Application)
(HAN Headquarters, Paris)
[sighs]
(Miyeong) I thought you'd like the idea.
[laughs awkwardly]
What is it?
Is it because of Mr. Kang?
[calm music]
[faint sigh]
He's already having a hard time
because of Mr. Choi.
I feel like I'd just make it worse.
[Miyeong reacts]
(Miyeong) Well, it's true
the timing isn't that great...
But if you give up?
Would you be okay with that?
You should think about
what you truly want.
[music stops]
[faint sigh]
[emotional music plays]
(Hagi) Sungwook said...
that he hated how he felt
toward someone he should be supporting.
[deep sigh]
It sounded like how I felt.
[faint sigh]
I know it's a good opportunity
for Ms. Nam,
but I don't want her to go.
And I feel so pathetic
for feeling that way.
[sighs]
I should be used...
to people leaving me by now,
but it's still hard for me.
(Minwoo) Then...
[pouring]
just ask her to stay.
If I stop her from going
just because of me,
[clunks]
then I'd be holding her back
from her dreams.
Wow!
[taps]
I should let her go.
[deep sigh]
That's the right thing to do.
[sighs]
You're hopeless.
[taps]
[clunks]
[sighs]
[Hagi grunts]
(Minwoo) Hey, be careful.
[Minwoo inhales]
[Hagi grunts]
[cheerful music]
Hey, get a grip.
- (Hagi) Hey...
- (Minwoo) Kang Hagi!
Kang Hagi!
Hey. I'm fine.
(Hagi) I mean it, I'm fine.
Let's go for another round!
My place!
(Minwoo) You have to make
a drunk confession.
You can't get wasted!
All right.
I'm going to do it!
Drunk confession!
- Okay.
- (Hagi) Let's do this!
[Minwoo grunts]
(Dareum) Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang.
[Dareum gasps]
[whoosh sound]
(Hagi) What?
[Dareum, Minwoo laugh awkwardly]
(Dareum) You can go ahead.
- It's Ms. Nam.
- (Dareum) Yeah...
[laughs]
Ms. Nam.
Yeah...
(Hagi) Ms. Nam.
[comical sound]
[reacts]
(Dareum) What?
[comical sound]
[reacts]
So cute.
[Dareum grunts]
[comical sound]
[reacts]
(Hagi) You're so cute, Dareum.
(Dareum) Oh...
I guess he's pretty drunk.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
[Dareum groans]
How can I send you away
when you're so cute?
[laughs awkwardly]
[comical sound]
[exclaims]
Give me a kiss.
[kissing sound]
[Hagi groans]
[Dareum grunts]
(Minwoo) Are you kidding me?
[comical sound]
[music stops]
Do it at home!
[Dareum exclaims]
Mr. Kang! Are you okay?
[Minwoo groans]
[intriguing music]
(Minwoo) I've never seen him
so drunk before.
[Dareum grunts]
[Minwoo laughs awkwardly]
(Minwoo) Let's take him home first.
(Dareum) One, two, three!
[Dareum, Minwoo grunt]
- (Minwoo) Let's go.
- (Dareum) Are you okay?
(Hagi) Yeah. Someone just hit me, though.
- (Minwoo) No.
- (Dareum) No one hit you.
(Minwoo) Let's go.
[music fades]
[insects chirping]
[Dareum sighs]
(Dareum) Why are you so...
(Hagi) You should go too.
I'm really fine.
[Dareum grunts]
[Hagi coughs]
Why do you keep telling me to go?
Here. Sit here for a moment.
[Hagi coughs]
[Dareum gasps]
[lively music]
[plops]
Mr. Kang?
[music stops]
(Dareum) Mr. Kang?
[faint laugh]
[Dareum grunts]
[sighs]
(Hagi) Don't go...
Don't go, Dareum.
[calm music]
[exhales]
[faint sigh]
(Minwoo) He's not okay with it at all.
He just doesn't want to hold you back.
[faint sigh]
[music stops]
(Notebooks, toiletries)
(Contact lens solution, cotton swabs)
[emotional music]
(Neck pillow, supplements,
pain relief spray, instant noodles)
(Things to pack for Paris)
[music stops]
[wind blowing]
(Wontae) Should we confirm these colors
for the brand, as you said?
(Hyesu) The colors seem too light.
What about this color for the jacket?
(Miyeong) Ms. Nam took the day off.
The application deadline's today,
but she hasn't applied yet.
[faint sigh]
[street noise]
[door opens]
[slurps]
[door closes]
[ding sound]
[bag rustles]
(One, two, three, four, five,
let's do this)
[calm music]
(fans) D.N.X, D.N.X, D.N.X!
[fans chant "D.N.X"]
- (Hyeok) One.
- (Lee Chan) Two.
- (Jinu) Three.
- (Taeo) Four.
Five. Let's do this!
(members) Let's do this!
(One, two, three, four)
(Five, let's do this)
[Dareum sighs]
(Dareum) I feel so relaxed
after deciding not to go.
[street noise]
[sighs]
[sips]
[Dareum exclaims]
Right. What's so special
about Paris anyway?
My friends are here,
APPELLO is here...
(Hagi) From now on, whatever happens,
[whoosh sound]
[soft music]
don't let go of my hand.
[Dareum laughs]
(Dareum) Okay.
[whoosh sound]
[faint laugh]
And Mr. Kang is here too.
Right, Nam Dareum.
You made the right choice!
[exclaims]
That's sweet.
[Dareum sighs]
[music stops]
[insects chirping]
[faint dog barking]
[faint sigh]
[faint laugh]
[soft music]
So you were alive.
[faint laugh]
(Roy) Chan.
[laughs]
(Lee Chan) I should have at least
been there for you.
I'm sorry.
[music stops]
(Roy) Why would you feel sorry?
[Lee Chan sighs]
I let go of your hand.
No, you didn't.
I'm the one who ran away.
[faint laugh]
[wistful music]
[Lee Chan sighs]
(Lee Chan) You would've been
the most scared,
but I guess I was too young at the time.
I ran away as well.
Let's...
stop running away.
Come back, Roy.
[exhales]
Would they...
accept me?
[inhales]
They swear whenever your part plays
during practice.
(Lee Chan) They pretend to hate you,
but they're waiting for you.
You saw the ad, right?
[taps]
That's how they actually feel.
[laughs]
[Roy sniffles]
[sniffles]
[faint laugh]
[Lee Chan, Roy laugh]
[music stops]
[pats]
[phone vibrating]
(Hagi) You know the application deadline
is today, right?
I'll wait until you come.
[calm music]
[Dareum gasps]
[wind blowing]
[sighs]
[taps]
(You know the application deadline
is today, right?)
(I'll wait until you come)
[thuds]
[faint sigh]
[door opens]
[Dareum pants]
Ms. Nam.
You were really waiting for me?
(Hagi) Yes.
[sighs]
[wind blowing]
(Hagi) You didn't submit your application.
[music stops]
You made me worry all day.
You...
were pretending to be fine with it too.
(Dareum) Did you think I wouldn't notice?
I'm a pro at pretending to be okay.
[Dareum laughs awkwardly]
Is that why you ran away?
No.
(Dareum) It's because
I love working with you,
eating with you,
and spending time with you.
That's why.
I just want to stay by your side.
Ms. Nam.
(Dareum) If I have to choose,
I choose you.
[calm music]
You're right.
[sighs]
(Hagi) I didn't want to send you away.
I was worried that we might end up
being separated
for good.
But I guess...
my love for you is bigger than my anxiety.
What I hated more
was the idea of you not going
because of me.
When you talked about Paris,
your eyes sparkled.
That was the expression
I fell in love with.
That excited, happy expression.
I want you...
to keep living with that expression.
So don't worry about me and go.
Look at lots of things,
[music stops]
and experience lots of things.
It will help you
do what you want even better.
You won't just let go of me...
because I'm leaving, right?
Of course not.
I'm going to hold onto you even tighter.
[tender music]
(Hagi) Let's put...
our faith in each other.
[faint laugh]
Okay?
(Dareum) Okay.
[faint laugh]
[wind blowing]
[music stops]
[murmuring]
(Mina) Congratulations, Ms. Nam.
I can't believe you're going to Paris.
That's so cool.
[Dareum laughs]
(Yeongwoo) Promise to upload photos
in our group chat.
[Dareum reacts]
(Miyeong) You have to come back, okay?
Yes. I promise to keep in touch.
- (Yeongwoo, Mina) Cheers!
- (Dareum) I'll miss you.
(Jinsang) Hey, what about us?
Don't leave us out!
[cheerful music]
- (Dareum) Cheers.
- (employees) Cheers!
I...
(Hagi) have something to tell you all.
(Dareum) Oh, my gosh!
[taps feet]
Mr. Kang!
To be honest...
[Dareum gasps]
(Hagi) Ms. Nam and I...
[Dareum sighs]
(Miyeong) We know, Mr. Kang.
[comical side effect]
[music stops]
(Mina) Wow. Congratulations.
(Wontae) Congratulations.
[employees cheer]
(Jinsang) Finally.
[cheerful music]
I haven't finished talking yet...
(Jinsang) Do you know how tiring it was
to pretend not to notice you two?
(Hyesu) Yeah. It was exhausting.
(Wontae) Seriously.
(Yeongwoo) It was funny
seeing your awkward acting.
[everyone laughs]
We won't be able
to have gatherings for a while.
It was always just the two of us anyway...
[comical sound]
[Jinsang coughs]
(Jinsang) Coke...
[coughing]
Can you give me some Coke?
[bell ringing sound]
[employees talking]
(Dareum) Mr. Kang...
[music stops]
[laughs awkwardly]
[Dareum, Hagi laugh]
(members) One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four...
- (Hyeok) Wait. Chan.
You're half a beat fast.
No, I moved at "two, two."
- (Lee Chan) I moved at "two."
- (Jinu) Both of you were fast.
- (Taeo) Again.
- (Lee Chan) What...
(Taeo) You were both wrong,
so get back in position.
- (Hyeok) Hey, Taeo...
- (Lee Chan) Okay, fine. I got it wrong.
- Let's do it again.
- (Hyeok) Taeo, you know it's...
- (Taeo) That's not it.
- (Jinu) Hurry up.
[tender music]
You're here.
I'm a bit late, aren't I?
[sighs]
We've been waiting for you...
[laughs]
(Jinu) I missed you!
(Taeo) Me too...
(Jinu) Let me see your face.
How have you all been?
(Jinu) Hey, what have you been through?
What happened to your idol face?
- (Hyeok) Right?
- (Taeo) He looks better than you guys.
What are you saying?
[Roy laughs]
(Lee Chan) Hey!
[members exclaim]
[members cheer]
(Lee Chan) What took you so long?
[music stops]
(The Collegeist pop-up has ended)
[D.N.X's "Dear My Light" plays]
[taps]
Can you play this song?
(Dareum) What?
[laughs]
[fan song "YOU" plays]
(Lee Chan in song) When the world
shakes me
And I lose myself
In every moment and every place
We'll dream together again
What do you think?
Only you
It's good.
(Lee Chan) That's it?
[laughs awkwardly]
It feels strange.
[faint laugh]
(Dareum) You're saying
those words to your fans,
but they're words
I wanted to say to you too.
[Dareum laughs]
(Lee Chan) So...
[music stops]
you're saying it's a pass?
[Dareum grunts]
[Dareum, Lee Chan laugh]
[sighs]
We both held on for a long time.
(Dareum) What? That's...
[soft music]
[gasps]
(Dareum) This...
[whoosh sound]
is actually the shape
that a celebrity I love
always draws in his autograph.
Today's my birthday,
and I really want to gift that to myself.
(Lee Chan) Excuse me!
Happy birthday.
[Lee Chan laughs]
(Lee Chan) It was me.
[whoosh sound]
The one who gave you that pendant
on your birthday.
[gasps]
[faint laugh]
Seeing you still keep that...
gave me the courage to go back onstage.
[exhales]
I stayed strong,
believing that you gave this to me.
[rattles]
(Dareum) I...
think I know what I really want
to do now.
Just like how I was happy as your fan,
I...
also want to do something
that would make
people's hearts race.
[inhales]
That's why you're going to Paris, right?
(Dareum) Yes.
Though I'm not sure
if I can do a good job.
I'm sure you'll do great.
(Lee Chan) I've seen...
how sincere you are.
[laughs awkwardly]
I was happy to know that I had
such an amazing fan.
So you should try
making other people's hearts race too.
[laughs]
[faint laugh]
[exhales]
[music stops]
[faint dog barking]
Passport.
Check.
[cheerful music]
(Hagi) Guidebook.
[taps]
(Dareum) Check.
Basic medicine.
[faint laugh]
[taps]
(Dareum) You packed
a whole pharmacy for me.
[Hagi sighs]
(Hagi) Will this be enough?
(Dareum) I'm not going to Paris
to sell medicine.
I just don't want you to get sick.
[scoffs]
[Dareum inhales and grunts]
[taps]
I think I've got everything.
[music stops]
[rustles]
(Hagi) You hung...
the keychain we made.
[Dareum laughs]
(Dareum) I'm going to take this with me
so I'll feel like you're with me.
[soft music]
Are you touched?
Yeah, a bit.
A bit?
A lot.
[laughs]
[Dareum inhales and grunts]
[clunks]
I should leave something behind
for you too.
(Hagi) What?
That's a secret. I'll tell you later.
[Dareum laughs]
[Hagi reacts]
[Dareum sighs]
I'll be back soon.
I'll be waiting for you.
[kisses]
[music stops]
(Dareum, Hagi)
[airplane engine sound]
(6 months later)
[writing sound]
[street sounds]
[lively music]
(secretary) [in French] Dareum,
Ms. Han wants this version by three.
(Dareum) Three? Today?
(secretary) Yes. You know what she's like.
[in Korean] Gosh...
She really is a Korean, isn't she?
(secretary) [in French] You can do it.
[in Korean] You can...
[laughs]
(Dareum) Do it.
(secretary) Yes!
[Dareum, secretary laugh]
[sighs]
[mouse clicking]
[exclaims]
All done.
[music stops]
[faint laugh]
[sighs]
[door opens]
[door lock sound]
[door closes]
[emotional music]
[sighs]
[clunks]
[ding sound]
(Dareum) Missions for Hagi
while waiting for me.
Water our plant and open the window
to give it sunlight.
[ding sound]
When a new leaf grows,
take a selfie with it and send it to me.
[camera snapping sound]
Show me the buds
on a video call when they appear.
[faint sigh]
[taps]
- (employee 1) [in English] Bye.
- (Dareum) Bye-bye.
[music stops]
[Dareum laughs]
[phone vibrating]
[Dareum gasps]
[taps]
[laughs]
[in French] Hi!
[cheerful music]
(Hagi) [in Korean] It's the weekend.
Are you at work?
[sighs]
[Dareum groans]
(Dareum) Yes!
Ms. Han really is no joke.
She gives me mountains of work.
She's even worse than you.
(Hagi) But why do you look so happy?
[Dareum laughs]
(Dareum) It's tough, but it's fun.
If it's tough but still fun,
that means you're doing a good job.
(Dareum) Gosh...
[laughs awkwardly]
You really talk like a CEO.
(Hagi) Well, I am a CEO.
[Dareum scoffs]
(Dareum) What about APPELLO?
Is everything going well?
(Hagi) Right. I just found out yesterday
that Park Yeongwoo
and Lee Mina are dating.
(Dareum) Really?
I knew they'd end up dating.
Since when?
(Hagi) Last week.
[Dareum gasps]
(Dareum) No way.
How did you find out?
(Hagi) It was just so obvious.
They're the only ones who don't know.
[laughs]
It was the same for us, you know.
[Hagi laughs]
(Hagi) Right. Look at this.
I think it'll bloom soon.
Wow, it's so pretty!
[swish sound]
(Dareum) How are you so good at this?
[ding sound]
I always killed off my plants.
[whoosh sound]
- (Hagi) You're grateful, aren't you?
- (Dareum) Yeah.
[Dareum laughs]
(Hagi) Then give me a reward.
[Dareum reacts]
[kissing sound]
[ding sound]
[Dareum laughs]
[Hagi laughs]
I miss you.
(Hagi) Me too.
[laughs]
[music stops]
[sparkling sound]
[Dareum grunts]
(Minwoo) Dareum will go
to the concert venue herself,
and I can take you there.
How will Seula come?
[beeping sound]
Will she come alone?
Or should I give her a ride?
[playful music]
[taps]
[grunts]
[whoosh sound]
Keep your eyes ahead.
[warning beep sound]
Eyes ahead.
[screeching sound]
[music fades]
(Minwoo) Eyes ahead.
(Seula) Hi, this is Fan Goods Shop.
[rustling]
[lively music]
Oh, yes. The slogan banners?
"Take all my money, Hoon"?
We're out of stock at the moment.
"You stole my heart, Min"?
This will be back in stock tomorrow.
150 of those? Okay.
All right.
Yes, of course. They'll be ready soon.
Okay!
(Lee Chan) One, two, three.
[members chant]
[members cheer]
Nice.
(D.N.X Reunites for Full Group Comeback)
[whoosh sound]
[Dareum gasps]
[intriguing sound]
(Dareum) I can't believe it!
[gasps]
[employees laugh]
[music stops]
[clapping]
(Miyeong) All right, everyone!
You know what it is, right?
[employees exclaim]
(Jinsang) It's time!
(Miyeong) All right!
This is a rite of passage
for every new employee at APPELLO.
So, Chaeeun.
Are you Team Mr. Kang?
Or Team Director Lee?
Or Team Jinsang?
[ding sound]
[employees boo]
[snaps]
[Jinsang grunts]
[employees laugh]
(Jinsang) I'm sure there's someone...
- (Miyeong) Shh! Quiet!
- (employee 2) There's no one.
[Chaeeun clears throat]
Well...
[exciting music]
[Chaeeun groans]
[Chaeeun continues groaning]
[ding sound]
Team Mr. Kang.
[employees gasp]
[chattering]
[Mina laughs]
(Yeongwoo) She used to be
Team Mr. Kang too.
[intriguing music]
[Yeongwoo groans]
I'm Team Yeongwoo now.
That hurt.
(Jinsang) I told you not to show off
that you're dating.
(Hyesu) Jeez...
[employees laugh]
- (Chaeeun) By the way...
- (Miyeong) Yes?
Is Mr. Kang single?
[employees sigh]
(Hagi) Yes.
[music stops]
Compile the preferred-brand data
separately for the US and Europe.
[footsteps echo]
[uplifting music]
[music stops]
(Chaeeun) I mean, he's always working...
[Jinsang laughs]
(Jinsang) All right!
[snaps]
[in a singing voice] Shall I tell you
whether he's dating someone or not?
[Jinsang pants]
Oh, I'm sorry, sir...
[employees laugh]
- (employee 2) I knew this would happen.
- (Jinsang) Gosh.
(Dareum) Too bad.
He's seeing someone.
[uplifting music]
[employees gasp]
(Yeongwoo) Ms. Nam!
[employees cheer and clap]
(Dareum) I've just returned to Korea!
(Wontae) What?
[Dareum cheers]
[sounds grow silent]
(Yeongwoo) When did you get here?
Wow!
[music stops]
Weren't you coming tomorrow?
I came a day early.
Why?
[faint laugh]
Because I missed you.
[employees cheer]
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
[Dareum laughs]
[music stops]
[sighs]
I'm really home.
There's something we haven't done yet.
[laughs]
[emotional music]
[Dareum laughs]
(Dareum) This must be why...
I wanted to come back.
[sighs]
[wind blowing]
[birds singing]
[music stops]
(Wonbin) The employee in charge
of this project
will present some fan merch proposals
for our comeback.
Who's the employee?
[door opens]
[door closes]
[papers rustle]
- (Dareum) Hello.
- (members) Hello.
(Dareum) Hello.
[upbeat music]
I'm Nam Dareum,
and I'll be working with you
on the D.N.X collaboration project.
Nice to meet you all!
[members clap]
[Jinu cheers]
(Wonbin) We look forward
to working with you.
Then shall we begin?
(Dareum) For this collaboration,
we took inspiration
from the fan song "YOU."
We wanted to reflect
your gratitude to the fans
who have waited for you in the merch.
As you can see here,
we planned three types,
T-shirts, tote bags, and caps.
Starting with the T-shirt,
you'll notice that
there are special details.
On the left chest pocket,
closest to the heart,
there are lyrics from the fan song
embroidered in elegant lettering.
[members talking]
[music stops]
(Lee Chan) You were really cool today.
Come on. You're flattering me.
[laughs awkwardly]
I mean it.
(Lee Chan) We're really
working together now.
(Dareum) That's why I have to do my best.
I won't be working on this project
just as a fan.
Then?
I'm an employee
who understands your fans as well.
[exclaims]
(Lee Chan) Then I look forward
to working with you,
Ms. Nam Dareum.
[soft music]
(Dareum) All right, Mr. Lee Chan.
(Lee Chan) All right.
[Lee Chan, Dareum laugh]
- Let's do this.
[door closes]
(Hagi) That was...
a great briefing.
[laughs awkwardly]
You heard?
[music stops]
I could hear everything outside.
(Hagi) You had such a confident voice.
[laughs awkwardly]
I think you're ready
for a bigger project now.
Are you trying to make me work overtime
after complimenting me?
I can't work late today.
Why?
I'm going on a date with my boyfriend.
[bright music]
[poking sound]
[popping sound]
[ding sound]
(Dareum) I think...
the fans would like this...
and this the most among the lyrics.
[Yeongwoo snaps fingers]
- (Chaeeun) Okay.
- (Dareum) Okay.
(Yeongwoo) Then it'll...
look like this. Ta-da.
[gasps]
(Dareum) Looks good.
(D.N.X Concert Outfit Reference Designs)
(Stage outfit-inspired merch)
[taps]
(Dareum) This is the most difficult.
[phone vibrating]
[rattles]
(Manager Na Wonbin)
[music stops]
Yes, Mr. Na.
(Dareum) What?
[Wonbin sighs]
(Wonbin) Someone...
posted a threat to attack the venue.
It's most likely just a prank,
but the police are going
to search the entire venue.
So the booking has been canceled.
[Miyeong sighs]
And the place we found in a hurry is...
[Wonbin sighs]
[tapping keyboard]
This place.
[Mina reacts]
It's pretty small, isn't it?
(Hagi) The stage is really close
to the audience.
[employees grunt]
So it looks like the stage outfits
will be changed too.
Then our outfit-inspired merch...
(Wonbin) Yes. I'm sorry.
Please design them
to match the new outfits.
[employees exclaim]
[sighs]
[calm music]
[faint sigh]
[sighs]
[Dareum inhales]
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
[whoosh sound]
(Hagi) Announce the venue change
across all available channels.
[tapping keyboard]
(Showcase venue change announcement)
(Mina) Let me check.
You only need to send
half of the display racks.
[whoosh sound]
(Hagi) It's an invitation-only showcase,
so please set up a registration link.
(D-Angel 1st Fan Club President)
[Miyeong exclaims]
[whoosh sound]
I haven't felt this fired up in ages.
[mouse clicking]
[Miyeong sighs]
[taps keyboard]
(Miyeong) Attention, D-Angels!
This is the real venue
for D.N.X's showcase.
Check the link and hurry!
[tapping sound]
[tapping keyboard]
[mouse clicking]
(Your post has been uploaded)
[exclaims]
[bubble popping sounds]
[whoosh sound]
[ding sounds]
[fans murmur]
[whoosh sound]
(Miyeong) Hello. Take one of these.
Have fun.
Hello. Take one of these.
- Have fun!
- (Wontae) Wow.
- (Mina) It's this, right?
- (Wontae) Did you make that yourself?
(fan 1) Yes...
[Mina, Wontae exclaim and clap]
- (Chaeeun) Enjoy the showcase.
- (Yeongwoo) Thank you.
(fans) Our president!
[Miyeong gasps]
(fan 2) It's been such a long time.
- (fan 3) We came after seeing your post.
- (Miyeong) Really?
- You saw it?
- (fans) Yes!
- (Miyeong) Wow!
- (Yeongwoo) Wow.
- (Miyeong) Here, take this.
- (fan 2) Thank you.
(fan 3) We'll cheer as loud as we can.
[music stops]
[murmuring]
[Lee Chan clears throat]
(Wonbin) Everyone.
You have to wear the APPELLO merch now.
[Wonbin laughs]
- (Dareum) Hello.
- (members) Hello.
(Dareum) Let's do this.
[members clap]
Ta-da!
(members) Wow.
[Dareum laughs]
[calm music]
[members, Wonbin exclaim]
[members exclaim]
[Dareum laughs]
(Roy) It's pretty.
It's like a shooting star.
This is...
(Dareum) Yeah.
The venue's a bit smaller,
but the fans would be happy
to see you up close.
[clinks]
So...
I just gave it a small detail.
The closest star.
[rattles]
Thank you...
for returning it to me like this.
[faint laugh]
You should shine onstage again.
[Wonbin exclaims and claps]
(Wonbin) Awesome.
[Lee Chan sighs]
Are you ready?
[sighs]
What about our fans?
(Lee Chan) Did a lot of them come?
Go and see for yourself.
[music stops]
[commotion]
(Mimi) I can't believe
we're actually here!
And we're watching at the front!
(Seula) My heart's about to explode...
Roy will do a good job, right?
I...
believe in Roy...
the performance genius!
I know he can do it.
[playful music]
(Minwoo) Who's your bias, Mimi?
(Mimi) Well, Chan got me into the fandom,
but I was crazy about Hyeok for a while.
What about now?
Minwoo.
[whistling sound]
[laughs]
All right, then.
[Minwoo laughs]
(Seula) Hey!
[whoosh sound]
[cat hissing sound]
Go be lovey-dovey at home, darn it.
Today's the day...
that my bias returns to the stage.
It's a historic day.
[Seula laughs]
[Minwoo grunts]
(Minwoo) Let's go.
[Minwoo laughs]
[music stops]
[Hyeok sighs and claps]
(Hyeok) All right.
Our fans have waited for nine years.
Let's give it everything we've got.
[members react]
[uplifting music]
- (Hyeok) One.
- (Lee Chan) Two.
- (Jinu) Three.
- (Taeo) Four.
Five. Let's do this!
(members) Let's do this!
[whoosh sound]
[music stops]
[fans murmur]
(Minwoo) One, two, three.
[Dareum gasps]
[fans cheer]
[D.N.X's "Neverland" plays]
[Dareum exclaims]
[Dareum cheers]
[D.N.X's "New Shirt" plays]
[fans cheer]
[D.N.X's "Dear My Light" plays]
[music stops]
[lights click]
[fans cheer]
Hyeok!
[Minwoo cheers]
(Mimi) Hyeok!
(Minwoo) You're so cool!
[lights click]
[fans cheer louder]
[Dareum cheers]
(fans) D.N.X!
D.N.X!
[fans chant "D.N.X"]
[wistful music]
[Lee Chan grunts]
(Lee Chan) We put a lot of thought
into what our first song should be.
Firstly...
thank you so much
for waiting all these years.
[fans cheer]
[Dareum cheers]
This song...
is for all of you,
who helped us come together
and perform onstage again.
[fans cheer]
[music stops]
The title...
is "YOU."
[shining sound on screen]
[fans cheer]
[fan song "YOU" intro plays]
Perhaps everything that shines
(Lee Chan) Will fade away someday
Dreaming used to be a part of who I am
[fans cheer]
But now, I'm just getting through each day
(Roy) The gazes on me
Waiting for the cheers
It makes me uneasy
Like walking on thin ice
- Close my eyes, fall asleep
- (Dareum) You're so cool!
Sometimes everything comes crashing down
But I'm here now
(Lee Chan) Only you, only you
Make me exist
[fans cheer]
When the world shakes me
And I lose myself
- (Hyeok) In every moment and every place
- (Mimi) Hyeok!
(Hyeok) We'll dream together again
(Lee Chan) Only you
Make me exist
[fans cheer]
[members sing "YOU"]
(Five stars shining again
D-Angel will be with you forever)
[members continue singing "YOU"]
[fans cheer]
(Seula) Roy!
(Dareum) I once used to follow
a shining star.
[D.N.X cheers on screen]
[friends cheer]
But that star wasn't the only light
that guided my way.
[Dareum laughs]
There was another light
shining next to me
whenever I felt I was alone.
(Dareum) I think...
I have feelings for you.
(Hagi) From now on, whatever happens,
don't let go of my hand.
(Dareum) Now...
I know...
that stars aren't that far away.
All these lights...
are stars,
each shining in their own place.
(Lee Chan) Only you, only you
Make me exist
[fans cheer]
When the world
Shakes me and I lose myself
(Taeo) In every moment and every place
We'll dream together again
Only you
Make me exist
[fans cheer]
[members sing "YOU"]
(Dareum) And that when I became
a light for someone else,
I was also...
shining brightly.
[whoosh sound]
[music stops]
[birds singing]
[lively music]
[children shouting]
(Dareum) Bubbles.
[Dareum exclaims]
How pretty.
Dareum.
[Dareum gasps and exclaims]
(Dareum) This is so cute.
You like it?
(Dareum) Yeah!
I want a ring too, as a matching set.
[faint laugh]
No.
(Dareum) What?
It'll wither soon.
It's all for the fun of it.
(Dareum) I want a ring too.
With a big flower.
Where can we find some?
(Hagi) I want to give you this instead.
I...
want to be a place
for you to return to every day.
Will you...
stay by my side?
[sighs]
(Dareum) Yes.
[music stops]
[laughs]
I will.
Every day.
[music: "My Bias, My Boss" theme song]
(Hagi) Right!